[theme music playing]
Due to insufficient testimonies
and evidence submitted in court,
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo and Raul Torillo
are hereby declared innocent of the rape,
abduction, and illegal
imprisonment of Camia Cruz.
We all know why the case against
the Ardientes was dismissed.
Because they threatened
and had the witnesses killed
so no one could prove
the crimes they committed.
[Emilia] I'll silence Camia once
and for all to solve our problem.
Slow down, Emilia. Camia Cruz?
She's too high a risk to take right now.
[Julio] What are you doing in my office?
I want you to keep an eye on Madrigal.
Even if you have me killed now,
your husband will never love you!
Oh, well, you want more?!
Emilia, that's enough!
I can't stop myself from protecting you
when they're hurting you
right in front of me!
She did it to protect Camia.
I need to find out how they're connected.
[Julio] I can smell traitors
from a mile away.
Good work, Arnaldo.
We finally caught the rat.
Take him to the dungeon.
You bastard! I trusted you!
And this is how you repay me?!
[Ivy] I need to save Jepoy.
Is that how important Jepoy is to you?
Yes, Diego. He's done so much for me.
He's sacrificed a lot
just so I can carry out my plans.
Ivy's here. Can I bring her there?
Why? What are you up to?
[ominous music playing]
Uh… If Emilia looks for me,
please tell her I'm in the ladies' room.
Yes, ma'am.
[ominous music playing]
[action music playing]
[tense music playing]
[door opens]
Fabian. Where's Ivy?
She's in the restroom, ma'am.
Oh.
[action music playing]
Ivy?
Ivy, are you there?
[action music playing]
Ivy?
Is everything okay?
Fabian, get the keys.
Fabian!
Hurry up, will you?!
Sorry, ma'am.
Give me that!
Goodness! Why didn't you label your keys?
See which one opens the door! Hurry!
You're supposed to label them!
Good grief!
[Emilia] Goodness… Hurry up!
Never mind!
Give me that! Get out of my sight!
[action music playing]
[door opening]
Ivy!
My goodness!
-Emilia?
-I've been calling you out!
Why weren't you answering?
Oh, sorry! I didn't hear you because…
you know…
You look tense. Why are you sweating?
Um…
Because it's summer, but there's
no AC in your restroom.
You should have one installed.
Well, okay.
Anyway, are you busy today?
Not really. Why?
Good. You're coming with me then.
Where are we going?
It's a surprise. You'll see.
Let's go.
[ominous music playing]
Emilia, what is this place?
This is Papa's happy place.
Your father's happy place?
What are we doing here, then?
You'll see.
[tense music playing]
[deep breathing]
I must admit, Madrigal.
You really are tough.
-Papa.
-Yes?
I have someone with me. Surprise!
Oh!
[tense music playing]
Miss Aguas.
I just want you to see what we do…
to anyone…
who betrays the Ardientes!
[Jepoy coughing]
[retches]
I'm sorry, but I don't think
I should be seeing this.
Emilia, why did you bring me here?
Not so fast, Ivy.
You see, it's not every day
Papa allows visitors like you here.
I brought you here because I trust you,
because I know we're allies.
Only a selected few are allowed
by Papa to come here.
And if you're one of those few,
that means you're bonded
with the Ardientes.
You know what, Ivy?
I'm actually giving you a great honor
because I'm offering you the chance
to be truly a part of my family.
But then again, before that happens…
you will have to prove your loyalty to us.
Because if there's one thing I hate…
it's backstabbing traitors!
[tense music playing]
Kill the man in front of you.
Kill Madrigal in front of us…
to prove that we're no different.
Kill Madrigal!
Shoot the damn dog!
Do it.
[suspenseful music]
-[gunshot]
-[groans]
[Jepoy exhales sharply]
[chuckles]
Did I scare you?
[drops gun]
I won't taint my hands
just to prove my loyalty!
When I tell you to shoot him,
you will shoot him!
And that's an order!
Don't you dare tell me what to do, Emilia!
Because I'm not one of your
father's lackeys, unlike you!
Well, of course!
Not unless you're taking orders
from someone else, Miss Aguas.
Just what do you mean by that?
You know, my old man used to say…
if you truly want to know a person…
watch what they do and not what they say.
You distributed lands to the farmers…
defended Camia against my daughter Emilia…
and a host of other things
that you've done that left
a bad taste in my mouth.
Now, Miss Aguas…
It seems like you're not
who you say you are.
[tense piano music playing]
Tell me, Congressman.
Why are you so paranoid?
[chuckles]
All my life, my family and I
have been bombarded
on all sides by unseen enemies.
Now, please. Humor me, Miss Aguas.
Even just once, let me be able
to face my enemies…
and look at them straight in the eye.
You think I'm your enemy, Congressman?
You insult me. To the
highest degree, Congressman.
The next time you accuse
your biggest investor,
I won't think twice before
siding with your greatest rival.
Once that happens,
that's the only time
you can call me a traitor!
But for now, my word is as good as gold!
Gold melts!
Even if it melts, it is still gold.
[tense music playing]
[line ringing]
Mrs. Camia.
Hey, Diego.
Any updates? Where's Lily?
Mrs. Camia, please calm down.
She hasn't been answering my calls.
Diego, be honest.
Does this have something to do
with Jepoy's disappearance?
[tense music playing]
Yes.
She's with the Ardientes,
looking for Jepoy.
What?
I'll save you, Jepoy.
I'll get you out of here.
I'll fight for you like how you fight me.
I promise, Jepoy.
I'll save you.
After everything that
just transpired here…
I still don't trust that woman.
What if she tells everyone
we have Madrigal?
Our names will be caught
in another controversy.
What do you expect Emilia to do?
Lock Ivy Aguas up like Madrigal?
Should we lock up everyone you suspect?
-[loud thump]
-If that's what it takes
to keep this family afloat, yes!
Papa… none of us trust Ivy.
But unlike you, I know how
to sleep with the enemy.
I have to keep her close
to get information.
Arnaldo, keep an eye on Ivy Aguas.
I want you to watch her like a hawk.
Watch every move she makes.
Because, unlike your mother here
who thinks she's our ally,
treat her as if she's our greatest enemy.
I'm sorry, Emilia.
But your father
is just not the trusting type.
[action music playing]
I was right! Jepoy is with the Ardientes!
They have him locked
and tied up somewhere.
Emilia and Julio are
torturing him for information.
Ivy, you and Miss Camia need to leave.
It's too dangerous if Jepoy rats us out.
No. I know Jepoy. He won't betray us.
He'll stay loyal until his last breath.
I'll break Jepoy out. I know…
where they're keeping him.
I'll sneak in and get him.
How are you going to do that?
The Ardientes have their eyes on you.
I'll find a way!
[suspenseful music playing]
All right. Just follow that car.
I'll finally know if you're
really connected to Camia Cruz.
But I hope you're not.
I hope you're not.
Lily, dear.
I know how important Jepoy is to you.
But come home first.
We need to plan this carefully.
I'm begging you.
Positive, sir.
According to our intel,
that's Camia Cruz's house.
Mom…
[whispering] Arnaldo.
Stay on the road. Just keep driving.
Where is she going?
She went past the house.
Mom. Listen to me, Mom.
-Lily…
-I can't go there for now.
Don't leave the house,
and don't let anyone know
that I'm the one you're talking to.
What are you saying?
Is something wrong?
Just trust me, Mom.
If the Ardientes want to play,
then we'll play.
Let's see who wins.
[ominous music playing]
Faster, please.
Faster!
This means she's not connected
to Camia Cruz.
Let's go back.
What about Ma'am Emilia's orders?
[phone ringing]
-Hello, Ma.
-Hello, Arnaldo, son.
Any news on Ivy Aguas?
What's going on?
False alarm.
There's nothing unusual…
with Ivy, so I'm going home.
-No, you can't!
-What?
I can't follow Ivy the whole day.
I have work to do.
You will not come home
until you get information on Ivy
Aguas, understood?
Those are your grandfather's orders!
-Where are they?
-We lost them.
Maybe they took a shortcut, Sir.
Should we go back, Mayor?
No.
Let's find that car and follow them.
[dramatic music playing]
Diego.
I should've gone with her.
Diego, my daughter is a strong woman.
She's brave.
Ever since she was young.
And we know this more than anyone else.
We just need to…
trust that she can handle
whatever's thrown at her.
[tense piano music playing]
Be thankful that Ivy Aguas
didn't shoot you in the head.
But…
I'm not like Ivy.
Because I won't hesitate
to blow your brains out
if you don't tell me the truth.
Before that, let's play a game.
Hmm…
Do you want to play with this?
This?
Hmm…
Boring.
I think I prefer this.
Hmm?
Do you see this?
Ha!
[laughing]
Let's try it.
This might convince you to talk.
-[screaming]
-[evil laugh]
-Mayor…
-Where's Ivy?
-What is it? Mayor, wait--
-Ivy!
-Ouch. Mayor, wait! Mayor!
-Ivy! Don't touch me.
Mayor, you can't just barge
into our house like this.
-Search the whole house!
-Mayor, wait!
Search every corner in all the rooms.
You can't do that. Mayor!
-Mayor, you can't do this.
-Yes?
[Carlotta] Ivy.
Are you looking for me, Mr. Mayor?
-Ivy, I thought--
-You thought what?
You thought I wasn't here,
so you'd go through my house?
Where's your warrant?
[tense music playing]
I may be stubborn, Mr. Mayor…
because I won't kill someone
just to prove my loyalty.
But that doesn't mean that you
can treat me like a criminal.
Of all people, you?
And here I thought…
we were friends.
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
It's too late for that.
You've already hurt me.
I think it's for the best
if you leave my house…
before I sue you for trespassing.
You. Leave my house.
And you, Mr. Mayor, out.
[sighs]
Ivy.
-Do you have a smoke?
-No. Sorry, bro.
They haven't paid us yet.
You're out of funds too?
When's our next pay going to be?
I don't know.
-You must stop squandering.
-[Jepoy] Water.
-Water.
-He wants water.
-Give him water.
-Water, huh?
[grunting]
[tense music playing]
You want to fight?
[grunts]
He wants to fight.
All right.
[tense music playing]
[Ivy] Jepoy, thank you.
Ever since you rescued me
from that perverted driver…
you've always been there for me.
You never left me.
[somber music playing]
Thank you so much.
It is my fault.
You don't know how much
I worried about you.
For sure, Emilia's suspecting you now.
I need to do something.
Just make sure you won't
get yourself in danger, Jepoy.
-You've done so much for me.
-Ivy, you don't understand.
That's not enough because I love you.
[Jepoy] There's nothing
I wouldn't do for you, Ivy.
[somber music playing]
You have to get out of here, Jepoy.
Remember everything you learned
from Miss Prianka.
Ivy needs you.
Ivy needs you. Ivy needs you right now.
I need to endure this for Ivy.
Mom, what are you doing here?
I already told you
that you can't come here.
Lily, I won't feel at ease
until I make sure that you're safe.
Mom, I'm fine.
Just like I said earlier…
I'll do everything I can…
to save Jepoy.
How will you do that?
Mom, trust me.
What's important is I know
where they're hiding Jepoy.
Lily…
I know that you're strong and brave,
but I'm sure that place
will be heavily guarded.
I'm worried about you.
[tense music playing]
Mom, thank you.
But I'm sorry because
I've made up my mind.
I'll save my friend. I'll save Jepoy.
But you're right.
I need to figure out a way
to get back to that place
without the Ardientes' knowing.
[tense music playing]
Ma'am.
Nanny, please take this away.
I already lost my appetite.
Funny, Emilia.
Between us,
don't you think I'm the one
who should lose my appetite?
First of all, you tried
to force me to kill someone.
Second, you had your son follow me.
Ivy, I have to protect our bases.
It's that simple.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
[tense music playing]
A little friendly advice, Emilia.
Can you please stop being so paranoid?
Why don't you just show
the people of Ardiente
that you aren't that easily rattled?
I get what you're trying to say, but how?
Hold a celebration.
Something that…
can bring you closer
to the people of Ardiente.
Well, if you don't have
the budget, I can always donate.
-Is this a peace offering?
-Yeah.
So shall we start on the wine?
Sure.
Nanny, corkscrew please! Faster!
[police officer] What did you say?
The Ardientes are holding
their bodyguard hostage?
Under what grounds?
The Ardientes think
that Madrigal is a traitor.
That's a personal matter
between the Ardientes
and their bodyguard.
It will be difficult
to get involved
in that kind of case, Diego.
You should know. You're an Ardiente.
I'm not an Ardiente.
[action music playing]
Okay. I'll put it on record.
-Thank you.
-Okay.
[phone ringing]
Hello, Grandpa?
[Julio] Since I can't rely on
you when it comes to Miss Aguas,
I want you to do something else
to get rid of everyone I doubt.
Okay, Grandpa.
I'll take care of Camia Cruz.
You can count on me.
[action music playing]
[action music continues playing]
Miss Camia.
Are you expecting company?
No, why?
-[car roaring]
-[crickets chirping]
[tense music playing]
Sir, they've got bodyguards.
So what?
There are more of us.
Are you scared?
We'll just do a quick spot-check, ma'am.
Please stay here.
Please check the entire house. Move.
[tense music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
Go on. Break into the house.
[car alarm blaring]
Miss Camia, please go inside.
-What's going on?
-Get in.
-[car horn honking]
-[car alarm blaring]
-[alarm stops]
-[car horn honking]
[car horn honking]
I want you all to be more alert
and careful. Do you understand?
Espiritu, did you hear what I said?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Talk to your men.
Do it now.
Lily, you're the one
who needs to be careful.
Since you're always with the Ardientes.
Mom…
Ivy, what you're doing
is really dangerous.
Don't put your life at risk just for this.
Diego, you don't understand.
I need to save Jepoy.
What if you get caught?
Ivy, they'll hurt you.
I will never forgive myself
if something bad happens to you.
And I won't forgive myself
if I let them kill Jepoy.
[somber music playing]
He's my family.
He's my friend, like my brother.
Wouldn't you do the same
for your loved ones?
I need to help Jepoy. I will save Jepoy.
Ivy, I know I can't stop you.
But let me protect you at least.
I will help you.
Thank you, Diego.
[tense music playing]
-Ivy, I'll come with you.
-No, Diego.
Stay here.
We'll push through with the plan
until I get Jepoy out.
-But, Ivy…
-Diego!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I can protect myself.
It's more dangerous
if both of us head on inside.
We might get caught.
If they catch me,
I'll try my best to escape.
Diego, please understand.
Ivy, be careful.
[action music playing]
Jepoy.
Where did they take you?
-This is for you, my friend.
-[woman] Thank you.
You're welcome. Use it well, okay?
[Julio] I hope that can help you.
[Claire] Oh. Here. Here she is.
[Julio] Okay. Come back
if you need anything else.
[Emilia] Use all those medicines.
[Julio] If you need anything
else, don't hesitate to ask.
We're here if you need anything else.
-[Emilia] Sir, you flatter me.
-[Julio] You're welcome, ma'am.
Come back if you need anything else.
-Sir.
-Thank you.
Thank you, Congressman and Mrs. Emilia.
We don't believe
the accusations against you.
For us, the Ardientes are innocent.
-Thank you.
-After all you've done
to help us, it's fair how
you're dealing with criminals.
Thank you, ma'am.
Truth be told, we're very
grateful to you for trusting us.
You're the reason we keep
doing what we do.
Thank you.
Thank you, everyone. Rest assured that--
Emilia. Since you're a true Ardiente…
I believe it's only right
for you to accommodate our townspeople.
-Thank you, Papa.
-By all means, please.
[action music playing]
Ivy, are you okay?
What happened?
Jepoy isn't there. Jepoy's gone!
I don't know where the Ardientes took him!
Don't worry. We'll find him for sure.
I'll find him, Diego.
[ominous music playing]
I need to go to the Ardientes now.
Let's go.
Please come back. If you
need anything, come to us.
-All right.
-Oh, there's Ivy! Wait, Papa.
-Okay.
-Ivy, you're finally here.
Emilia.
You know, your idea is just so brilliant.
It's like we're making a statement
to our political rivals.
I'm glad you see it that way.
Maybe by now, Congressman,
you won't doubt me anymore.
Miss Aguas, never again.
All right, I'll just stay over
there so I won't bother you.
-Excuse me.
-Thank you again.
[tense music playing]
-[Emilia clears throat]
-[Julio] Did you invite her?
[Emilia] Yes, Papa. This was her idea.
Oh, I see.
The governor must be crying.
I don't know why they asked us
to transfer him.
Why don't you just admit it?!
Do you think anyone will come to save you?
[Jepoy grunts]
-Stay here.
-[Jepoy grunts]
[ominous music playing]
[phone ringing]
-Hello?
-[Arnaldo] Hello.
Have you moved him yet?
Yes, Mayor. We already did.
Okay, good.
Grandpa, Madrigal was
transferred to another hideout,
just as Mom ordered.
That's good to hear. Since more and more
of our enemies are popping up,
that was a good move.
You see, Emilia.
After all these years…
you eventually learned something from me.
[Emilia] Get your grandfather a chair.
Papa, I'll just stay there.
Okay, Emilia.
[Arnaldo] Grandpa, have a seat.
-Thank you, Arnaldo.
-I'll mingle with the people.
[Julio] Go ahead.
What did you do to Jepoy?
Is he still alive?
Where did you move him?
Where did you take him?
[action music playing]
Dad…
Dad, I saw your car outside
Miss Camia's house last night.
What were you doing there?
I heard the Ardientes
wanted to hurt Camia.
So I did something to trigger a search.
But you know the situation
you're in, right?
Miss Camia doesn't want to see you.
I know. But I can't sit back
and do nothing.
I'm doing everything I can to protect her.
[dramatic piano music playing]
I know you understand me, son.
Dad.
Dad, where are you going?
We've got plenty of medicines over there.
Just tell them what you need, okay?
-Thank you, Mayor.
-All right.
[Arnaldo] Get yours too.
Just tell us what you need.
[clears throat] Miss Aguas.
Uh, you seem quieter than usual.
Are you all right?
Tell me. I'll do what I can.
Mr. Mayor, to be honest,
I really want to talk to you.
Have you already forgotten what you did?
Yes, about that…
Not here.
Let's talk somewhere else.
Let's go somewhere private.
I want you to myself.
If you don't mind.
[ominous music playing]
[goon] I feel sorry for Madrigal.
He looks horrible. He can't even stand.
Forget about him.
Let's go, I'm starving!
Let's take a break.
Sure.
[ominous music playing]
[groans]
[grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[somber music playing]
Miss Aguas.
Mr. Mayor.
I think I owe you an apology.
I'm sorry for barging
into your house like that?
[sleazy music playing]
Let's not talk about it.
Okay, then.
What is it you want to talk about?
What's this?
What else? It's a security camera.
And I don't know
why I found one in my mansion.
But I think I know who put it there.
-Madrigal…
-Exactly! It's Madrigal!
I don't know why he put that
in my mansion. Why?
Just because I'm affiliated
with the Ardientes,
he'll go after me too?
[tense music playing]
Ivy, I'm sorry.
That man needs to be dealt with.
Yes, he needs to be punished.
I want to see him.
I'm so full.
What the? Where's Madrigal?
We're in big trouble.
Let's find him!
[action music playing]
To reciprocate the love
and trust you've shown the Ardientes,
starting today,
I'll be giving away rations
and allowances to all of you every day.
-[applauding]
-[cheering]
Wait, I know you're pleased
with what I said,
but I'm sorry I made a little mistake.
I'm sorry about that. I'm still human.
Maybe not every day
because I'll go bankrupt.
Every month, I promise
you'll receive rations
and allowances from us.
That is testimony
to the Ardientes' love for you,
especially mine,
for your kindness
and obedience as my children.
And now, to ask how everyone
in this town is doing,
I'd like to present to you, our trusted…
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo.
-[cheering]
-[applauding]
[tense music playing]
Thank you very much, Papa.
A round of applause
for our Señor Julio Ardiente.
-[cheering]
-[applauding]
A father to us all!
And yes, it's true that
my father has appointed me to--
[phone ringing]
Like I said, to serve you as--
[goon] Madrigal got away.
This can't be. Hold this.
-[Julio] Emilia!
-Emilia!
Emilia!
[action music playing]
[grunting, panting]
Madrigal! Stop!
[Jepoy grunts]
[unintelligible]
Get up! Get up!
[grunting]
Come here!
[screaming]
You know why I wanna him?
I wanna see him because I regret
not taking Madrigal's life
when Emilia gave me the chance!
He has some nerve doing this to me!
[somber music playing]
I understand.
You can still do it.
But Madrigal isn't
in his old detention room.
My mother had him moved.
You moved him?
Really?
Where?
They probably moved him
somewhere your mother
and grandfather can torture him even more.
I want to see Madrigal
being tortured with my own eyes
because he deserves it.
[tense music swelling]
Maybe…
It's time I took you to him.
[tense music playing]
I owe you one.
[tense music continues playing]
[somber piano music playing]
Raul dropped by again tonight.
[sighs] Good thing
he didn't cause trouble.
[somber piano music playing]
If you thought you could escape
without us knowing,
well, you were wrong! Idiot!
Let's see what else we can do with you.
Hmm…
How about this?
[drill whirring]
Hmm?
[chuckles]
Who do you work for?
Answer me!
Who's your boss?!
[drill whirring]
Emilia.
Stop playing games.
Torture him and get the answer we need.
Okay, Papa.
Hang him upside down! Now!
[suspenseful music playing]
Madrigal, I am not in the mood for games.
Do I have the time?
Now, this is going to be easy.
You will tell me who your boss is.
If you don't,
I'll drill this into your forehead
until your brains spill out,
and that will be
the death of you. Is that clear?
[suspenseful music playing]
[drill whirring]
[phone rings]
Hello, Mama?
Any news on Madrigal?
Who's his boss? Who does he work for?
[suspenseful music playing]
[Natalie] Everyone comes back
for a reason.
I still think about how my dad died.
I know someone had him killed,
and I wanna know who it is.
[Julio] You are of no use now, Madrigal.
Goodbye. Go ahead. Do it!
As long as I'm in power, no traitor
or rebel can ever bring
the Ardientes down!
[Diego] I'll run for governor.
I will do everything
in my power to help you win.
[theme music playing]